Can Elmo and Abby save Christmas?
Elmo's Christmas Countdown is a family, tv movie,
fantasy film directed by Gary Halvorson.
There's a miracle on Sesame Street in this special holiday tale.
Elmo, Abby Cadabby, and their new friend Stiller the Elf are going to
count down to Christmas with the Christmas Counter-Downer.
But all the counting boxes have gone missing and Christmas may never come again!
Elmo (voice), played by Kevin Clash.
Abby Cadabby (voice), played by Leslie Carrara-Rudolph.
Stiller the Elf (voice), played by Ben Stiller.
Papa Bear / Stan the Snowball (voice), played by Joey Mazzarino.
Prairie Dawn / Zoe (voice), played by Fran Brill.
Count von Count (voice), played by Jerry Nelson.
Elmo's Christmas Countdown is a 2007 television Christmas
special, featuring the characters from Sesame Street.
It was first aired on December 23, 2007, on ABC and starred Ben Stiller.
The tone is lighthearted.